time here be well
laying win
thought about works salvation today
that's a term that the internal security
cages like the years
there come up with an ingenious way
through a false accusation using that
are
to try to convince people that her
daughter is correct that is associated
with race
while the opposition is the worst
salvation and therefore wrong
each one is either once saved always say
or believing
in a later in all these wrong works LA's
they say the knowledge on security
people or
believing in ourselves nation trying
earners elevation or
involved in legal is we can speak for
everyone
that as for those was a revenge are all
rich
none all those labels apply to us
even though we do definitely hey and
recheck
each our own security or once saved
always saved as heretical
and demonic please know our faith and
trust
is it jesus what a hundred percent for
selfish
we believe we are saved by grace
and not by works if asians 289
but we also believe that a saving faith
in Jesus means we will have to have good
works
with our profession of faith in Jesus as
Jane's 240
and James 217 stay most people don't
know the same Greek word translated
works in the faces 29
is also in Chains 240
and James 270 referring to true
salvation
we see the same for truth
resurface again at once as low as 13
where the same Greek word translated
works
faces 29 is also file it says
quote worker faith I'm quell
King James or quote
work produced by faith i'm quoting an ID
to say Jesus has got works let
not allow the popular retail security
agers
confuse or deceive me about this
are going back to James for a minute he
also made another role to play
about I he talked about another time
faith-based
the Vincent J chapter two verse like a
not even snow there's one god
and the shower false as you how they
don't pay
don't be deceived following
Jesus were being caught as she did John
10:27 as absolutely
no connection whether we're selfish
upbeat the instant it got hit.
wrong way be quiet or worse elevation in
our
prostate our mansion at 64 he is the guy
which is basically Christianity is
downplayed and basically
cosby unattainable the aspirate ages of
it for our
and only teach at times that Christians
since all the time and even slanders the
Apostle Paul was being that
were style setters mansion the bottom
was clear he grows
well I now I that loves you have to tell
salvation all
they Jesus 20 quite upbeat he is still
works salvation
is not only on structural if fit
kak what is needed for salvation is
you're the only major Christian
sees a sense else said his spiritual
family are those who hear Oregon and
they put into practice Luke a twenty-one
and the Apostle John wrote this their
children dollar-a-day 18 years try
he loved us waters rise writers
justices rights it does we're set for
is I'll devil first John 387 today
but that's not all the Bible teaches one
must be wholly to enter
God's holy presence after death Matthew
5:8 speaks at the same salvation truth
with these worth lesson or other she
wore in the
heart they will see got Hess
Christians are tall to keep themselves
of your
and are constantly warned through the
eight estimate that certain sense we'll
send them to
hell if what doesn't inherit go asking
that
he will go to hell and since sex is less
faces 5527 glasses 5 19 to 21 sever
can cause that all they ain't got no
prefect committing success
should be mad if I don't stress not as
being legal as our our salvation or
outside grace
the truth there isn'ta security cagers
ever change grace into a license this
season and/or slandering their
opposition with the time works salvation
says teachers remain a major
hindrance and labels their christians
especially converse as they
twice biblical terms teach their
distortions
job was very clear when he gave us first
John chapter 234
we know that we have come to know if we
all they
his commands the man says I know him
but does not do what He commands is a
liar are and the truth as an RN jobs are
teaching a work cell
nation when he stressed simple obedience
as a sin salvation am boldly label
percent a liar if he says he knows Jesus
but it doesn't do what God commands the
Saint John
also gave us the Gulf ports are and
Chapter three for 36
he said your blazer size it out alive
for you does not obey
the sign sure I'll see life but the
wrath of God abides on him now that's
from the new
to American Standard Bible leaving on
Jesus
is a quiet without paying yeah
don't be deceived about the subject
simple obedience to God is
not were selfish it is the essence
up true saving faith insists
the bible does not teach it %ah security
or once saved always say it
don't let us teach is thus a few god
bless
home
good